Guide to the "Terry Sanford and the New South" records, 2000-2005 RL.10085
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Terry Sanford and the New South records
2000-2005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Lennon, Thomas Furneaux
RL.10085
5.5 Linear Feet 5 banker boxes, 1 cassette box
Terry Sanford and the New South, a documentary by filmmaker Thomas Lennon, examines Sanford's governorship in North Carolina during the Civil Rights movement and his vision of a New South. Sanford was governor of North Carolina, 1961-1965, and also served as President of Duke University, 1969-1985. This accession (2009-0169) (5.0 lin. ft.; 2000 items; dated 2000-2005) includes digital videotapes and duplicates from the production of Terry Sanford and the New South, as well as research notes, production notes and timelines, an index of filed images, and subject files for images used in the film. Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts. The finished documentary, Terry Sanford and the New South, can be viewed through NCLive, http://media.nclive.org/play_video.php?vid=383.
Provenance
The Terry Sanford and the New South records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2009.
Historical note
"Terry Sanford and the New South," a documentary by Thomas F. Lennon, examines Sanford's governorship in North Carolina during the Civil Rights movement and his vision of a New South. The film premiered in 2007 on PBS.
Sanford was governor of North Carolina, 1961-1965, and also served as President of Duke University, 1969-1985, and as a U.S. Senator, 1986-1993.
Thomas Furneaux Lennon is a an award-winning documentary filmmaker whose work includes Seven Days in Bensonhurst (1990), The Choice (1992), The Battle Over Citizen Kane (1996), The Irish in America (1998), Unchained Memories (2003), and Becoming American: The Chinese Experience (2003).
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Original audiovisual materials are closed to use. Use of these materials may require production of listening or viewing copies. Please contact Research Services before coming to use this collection.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Collection Overview
This collection (5.0 lin. ft.; 2000 items; dated 2000-2005) includes digital videotapes and duplicates from the production of "Terry Sanford and the New South," as well as research notes, production notes and timelines, an index of filed images, and subject files for images used in the film. Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts.
Compact discs; Audiovisual materials; Mini-DV; Documentary films; North Carolina -- History; Digital audio tapes; Duke University -- History -- 20th century; North Carolina -- Politics and government -- 1775-1865; North Carolina -- Politics and government; Civil rights movements -- North Carolina -- Durham; Lennon, Thomas Furneaux; Sanford, Terry
- Audiovisual materials, 2000-2005; 1; 2 Linear Feet 132 tapes in two boxes.
  - Interview with Bert Bennett, Tom Lambeth, and Joel Fleishman, 2003 July 23; 1
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 1 Tape 1, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0001)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 2 Tape 1, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0002)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 3 Tape 1, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0003)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 4 Tape 1, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0004)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 1 Tape 2, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0005)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 2 Tape 2, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0006)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 3 Tape 2, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0007)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 4 Tape 2, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0008)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 1 Tape 3, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0009)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 2 Tape 3, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0010)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 3 Tape 3, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0011)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 4 Tape 3, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0012)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 1 Tape 4, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0013)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 2 Tape 4, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0014)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 3 Tape 4, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0015)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 4 Tape 4, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0016)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 1 Tape 5, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0017)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 2 Tape 5, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0018)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 3 Tape 5, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0019)
    - Bennett/Fleishman/Lambeth Cam 4 Tape 5, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0020)
    - D1, Camera 1, Tapes 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, Bennett, Fleishman, Lambeth, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0005)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 1 Camera 2, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0016)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 1 Camera 3, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0017)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 1 Camera 4, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0018)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 2 Camera 2, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0019)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 2 Camera 3, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0020)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 2 Camera 4, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0021)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 3 Camera 2, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0022)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 3 Camera 3, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0023)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 3 Camera 4, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0024)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 4 Camera 2, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0025)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 4 Camera 3, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0026)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 4 Camera 4, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0027)
    - Sanford - 3 Person int., digital tape recording system backup (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL10085-DTRS-0001)
  - Interview with Quinton Baker, circa 2003; 11
    - Cam 2 - Tape 103, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0062)
    - Cam 2 - Tape 104, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0063)
    - D5, Camera 2, tapes 100, 101, 102, 103, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0009)
    - D6, Cam 2, tapes 104, 105, 106, Quinton Baker, Dickson Phillips, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0010)
  - Interview with Hugh Cannon, 2003 July 23; 2
    - Hugh Cannon, Cam 1 Tape 6, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0021)
    - Hugh Cannon, Cam 2 Tape 6, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0022)
    - Hugh Cannon, Cam 1 Tape 7, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0023)
    - Hugh Cannon, Cam 2 Tape 7, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0024)
    - Hugh Cannon, Cam 1 Tape 8, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0025)
    - Hugh Cannon, Cam 2 Tape 8, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0026)
    - Hugh Cannon int. 1, digital tape recording system backup (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL10085-DTRS-0002)
    - Hugh Cannon int. 2, digital tape recording system backup (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL10085-DTRS-0003)
    - D2, Camera 1, Tapes 6, 7, 8, 9, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0006)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 6 Camera 2, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0028)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 7 Camera 2, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0029)
  - Interview with David Cooper and Gene Roberts, 2003 September 26; 9
    - Cooper/Roberts, 2 shot, 200A, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0047)
    - Cooper/Roberts, close up, 200B, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0048)
    - Cooper/Roberts, 2 shots, 201A, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0049)
    - Cooper/Roberts, close up, 201B, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0050)
    - Cooper/Roberts, wide, 202A, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0051)
    - Cooper/Roberts, c/o, 202B, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0052)
    - Cooper/Roberts, wide, 203A, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0053)
    - Cooper/Roberts, c/u, 203B, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0054)
    - D7, Cooper/Roberts, Tape 200A, 2 shot, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0011)
    - D8, Cooper/Roberts, Tape 201A, 2 shot, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0012)
    - D9, Cooper/Roberts, Tape 202A, WS, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0013)
    - D10, Cooper/Roberts, Tape 203B, Close-Up, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0014)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 200 Camera B, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0039)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 201 Camera B, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0041)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 202 Camera B, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0040)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 203 Camera A, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0042)
  - Interview with Adisa Douglas and Miriam Dorsey, circa 2003; 6
    - Miriam Dorsey/Adisa Douglas, Cam 1 Tape 13, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0034)
    - Miriam Dorsey/Adisa Douglas, Cam 2 Tape 13, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0035)
    - Miriam Dorsey/Adisa Douglas, Cam 1 Tape 14, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0036)
    - Miriam Dorsey/Adisa Douglas, Cam 2 Tape 14, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0037)
    - D3, Camera 1, Camera 2, Tapes 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0007)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 13 Camera 1, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0031)
  - Interview with Vernon Jordan, John Edwards, and Jim Hunt, 2005 March 29; 13
    - Terry Sanford #1 Vernon Jordan, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0068)
    - Terry Sanford #2, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0069)
    - Terry Sanford #3, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0070)
    - Terry Sanford #4, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0071)
    - Terry Sanford #1 Vernon Jordan - clone, Mini-dv duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0072)
    - Terry Sanford #2 - clone, Mini-dv duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0073)
    - Terry Sanford #3 - clone, Mini-dv duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0074)
    - Terry Sanford #4 - clone, Mini-dv duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0075)
    - Terry Sanford #1 - Ikegami wide, DVCAM working copy (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0001)
    - Terry Sanford #2 - Ikegami wide, DVCAM working copy (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0002)
    - Terry Sanford #1 - Ikegami wide - clone, DVCAM working copy (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0003)
    - Terry Sanford #2 - Ikegami wide - clone, DVCAM working copy (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0004)
    - Terry Sanford DAT Audio backup #1, digital audio tape backup (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL10085-DAT-0001)
    - Terry Sanford DAT Audio backup #2, digital audio tape backup (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL10085-DAT-0002)
    - Terry Sanford DAT Audio backup #3, digital audio tape backup (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL10085-DAT-0003)
  - Interview with Reginald McCoy, 2003 July 25; 8
    - Reginald McCoy, Cam 1 Tape 18, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0044)
    - Reginald McCoy, Cam 2 Tape 18, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0045)
    - D4, Camera 2, Tapes 15, 16, 17, 18, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0008)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 18 Camera 1, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0034)
  - Interview with Roy Parker, Jr., 2003 July 25; 7
    - Roy Parker, Cam 1 Tape 15, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0038)
    - Roy Parker, Cam 2 Tape 15, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0039)
    - Roy Parker, Cam 1 Tape 16, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0040)
    - Roy Parker, Cam 2 Tape 16, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0041)
    - Roy Parker, Cam 1 Tape 17, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0042)
    - Roy Parker, Cam 2 Tape 17, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0043)
    - D4, Camera 2, Tapes 15, 16, 17, 18, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0008)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 15 Camera 1, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0032)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 17 Camera 1, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0033)
  - Interview with Dickson Phillips, circa 2003; 12
    - Cam 1 - Tape 105, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0064)
    - Cam 2 - Tape 105, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0065)
    - Cam 1 - Tape 106, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0066)
    - Cam 2 - Tape 106, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0067)
    - D6, Cam 2, tapes 104, 105, 106, Quinton Baker, Dickson Phillips, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0010)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 105 Camera 1, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0038)
  - Interview with Margaret Rose Sanford, circa 2003; 5
    - Margaret Sanford, Cam 1 Tape 11, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0031)
    - Margaret Sanford, Cam 2 Tape 11, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0032)
    - Margaret Sanford, Cam 2 Tape 12, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0033)
    - D3, Camera 1, Camera 2, Tapes 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0007)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 11 Camera 1, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0030)
    - Special - Margaret Rose Sanford "His Mother", Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0077)
  - Interview with Terry Sanford, Jr., circa 2003; 3
    - Terry Sanford, Cam 1 Tape 9, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0027)
    - Terry Sanford, Cam 2 Tape 9, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0028)
    - D2, Camera 1, Tapes 6, 7, 8, 9, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0006)
  - Interview with Terry Sanford, Jr. and Elizabeth Sanford, circa 2003; 4
    - Terry and Betsee Sanford, Cam 1 Tape 10, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0029)
    - Terry and Betsee Sanford, Cam 2 Tape 10, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0030)
    - D3, Camera 1, Camera 2, Tapes 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0007)
  - Interview with Roy Wilder, circa 2003; 10
    - Roy Wilder Pre-Interview, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0055)
    - Cam 1 - Tape 100, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0056)
    - Cam 2 - Tape 100, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0057)
    - Cam 1 - Tape 101, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0058)
    - Cam 2 - Tape 101, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0059)
    - Cam 1 - Tape 102, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0060)
    - Cam 2 - Tape 102, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0061)
    - D5, Camera 2, tapes 100, 101, 102, 103, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0009)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 100 Camera 1, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0035)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 101 Camera 1, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0036)
    - Protection dupe, Tape 102 Camera 1, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0037)
  - Associated footage, 2003-2005; 14
    - 300, Buckminster Fuller Lights, Mini-dv recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0076)
    - D11, Contains: 300, Buckminster Fuller Lights, DVCAM duplicate (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0015)
    - S10, R1-R6: UNC; R9: Budget; R23: WPA; R24: Grinberg; R25: UNC, DVCAM recorder original (Box 5, Video-cassette RL10085-DVCAM-0043)
    - N.C. Capitol - Senate B-roll, Tape 19, Mini-dv recorder original, 2003 July 25 (Box 6, Video-cassette RL10085-MDV-0046)
- Research and notes, 2000-2005; 1
  - Archives and library catalogs binder (Box 1)
  - Terry Sanford Project (2000) binder (Box 1)
  - Sanford still photographs not in show (2005) binder (Box 1)
  - Hugh Morton prints of Governor Sanford (Box 1)
  - Dickson Phillips interview transcript, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Scripts notes (Box 1)
  - Tom's selects (Box 1)
  - Terry Sanford timeline (Box 1)
  - Terry Sanford documentary notes (3 folders) (Box 1)
  - Photo research (Box 1)
  - Index of filed images, Aug. 2000 (Box 1)
  - The New South article, 1964, and miscellaneous (Box 1)
- Image files, 2000-2005; 2
  - Agricultural life, Black, NC, 1930s-1950s (Box 1)
  - Agricultural life, NC, 1930s-1950s (Box 1)
  - Agricultural life, Black, US, 1930s-1950s (Box 1)
  - Burt Bennett (Box 1)
  - Civil Rights, lunch counter sit-ins (Box 1)
  - Churches (Box 1)
  - Civil Rights, demonstrations (Box 1)
  - Construction, US, 1930s-1960s (Box 1)
  - Cotton farming, South, 1930s-1940s (Box 1)
  - Cotton farming, South, 1950s-1960s (Box 1)
  - Cotton farming, NC, 1930s-1940s (Box 1)
  - Depression, US (Box 1)
  - Duke University (Box 1)
  - Adisa Douglas (Box 1)
  - Ehle, John (Box 1)
  - Fayetteville (Box 1)
  - Fuller, Buckminster (Box 1)
  - Graham, Frank, campaign and Senate (Box 2)
  - Library of Congress (Box 2)
  - Lou Harris (Box 2)
  - Hodges, Luther (Box 2)
  - Industry, NC, 1930s-1940s (Box 2)
  - Kennedys (Box 2)
  - LBJ (Box 2)
  - Kent State (Box 2)
  - KKK (Box 2)
  - Lake, E. Beverly (Box 2)
  - Larkins, John Davis (Box 2)
  - Laurinburg (Box 2)
  - Labor unrest, NC, 1920s-1940s (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
  - New York City skyline (Box 2)
  - News and Observer printed and not selected (Box 2)
  - News and Observer stills (Box 2)
  - NC maps and buildings (miscellaneous) (Box 2)
  - NC Fund/NC volunteers (Box 2)
  - Paratroopers (Box 2)
  - Photos not looked through (Box 2)
  - Political organizations (Jaycees, Rotary, etc.) (Box 2)
  - Research Triangle Park (Box 2)
  - Rural life, Black, 1930s-1950s (Box 2)
  - Rural life, Black, 1960s-1970s (Box 2)
  - Rural life, NC, 1950s-1970s (Box 2)
  - Rural life, NC, 1920s-1940s (Box 2)
  - Sanford, 1950 campaign (Box 2)
  - Sanford, 1968 campaign (Box 2)
  - Sanford, 1972 campaign (Box 2)
  - Sanford, 1976 campaign (Box 2)
  - Sanford, WWII (Box 3)
  - Sanford, Miscellaneous late (Box 3)
  - Sanford, Senate (Box 3)
  - Sanford, Overseas trips (Box 3)
  - Sanford, Youth (Box 3)
  - Sanford, 1960 campaign (Box 3)
  - Sanford, 1960s miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - Sanford, Duke University (Box 3)
  - Sanford, 1986 campaign (Box 3)
  - Sanford, 1992 campaign (Box 3)
  - Sanford, family (Box 3)
  - Sanford, governorship (Box 3)
  - Schools, segregation, and integration, 1950s (Box 3)
  - Sanford and JFK (Box 3)
  - Sanford and LBJ (Box 3)
  - Schools, segregation, and integration, 1960s (Box 3)
  - Schoolchildren, US, 1920s-1940s (Box 3)
  - Schoolchildren, US, 1950s-1970s (Box 3)
  - Schoolchildren, NC, 1950s-1970s (Box 3)
  - Scott, Walter Kerr (Box 3)
  - Scouts (Box 3)
  - Segregation (Box 3)
  - Seawell, M. (Box 3)
  - Former slaves (Box 3)
  - Student protests (Box 3)
  - Supreme Court (Box 3)
  - Textile industry, US, 1930s-1940s (Box 3)
  - Textile industry, NC, 1930s-1940s (Box 3)
  - Textile industry, US, 1950s-1960s (Box 3)
  - Textile industry, NC, 1950s-1980s (Box 3)
  - Tobacco farming, NC, 1930s-1950s (Box 3)
  - Tobacco farming, US, 1930s-1950s (Box 3)
  - Tobacco farming, US, 1960s-1970s (Box 3)
  - UNC students, 1930s-1940s (Box 3)
  - UNC miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - Voting (Box 3)
  - Wallace, George, 1940s-1950s (Box 3)
  - Wallace, George, 1960s (Box 3)
  - Wallace, George, 1970s (Box 3)
  - Wallace, George, 1980s (Box 3)
  - Wallace, George, miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - Wilder (Box 3)
  - CDs - high resolution images with still shots of Terry Sanford (Box 4)